[Music]
I'm a little feverish and slightly
delirious phone dropping the chopping
noise next to where the speaker sits and
I can barely speak the spit still
with that reefer kid cheap and it even
that not wanting to give a roll up
through the police station peep the cops
face when a hot alien wave tells me she
raped him dude
Seraphin textures of the bottom half a
keyboard zoomed in on the middle saying
damn dude space is huge probably I be
found dead in my apartment how do you
eat when you lack little white part and
round up a cavewoman stomper out with
Doc Martin screaming bitch make me
dinner like a little white Cartman and
she's too low to get a face put on milk
carton baby buy the milk man no
abortion please can I keep it hold quit
your talking on the carriage she rocks
is off a cliff Clara Barton